CAMQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "A broader definition of dietary supplement includes culinary h____, s____, and f____",
        "answer": "herbs, spices, foods",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "A dietary supplement is intended to supplement the diet, contains one or more dietary ingredients, and is intended to be taken by mouth as a c____, p____, t____, l____, and is labeled on the front as a dietary supplement",
        "answer": "capsule, pill, tablet, liquid",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is NOt a reason for supplement use?",
		"choices": "convenience, cost, lack of access to medical care, trust of the medical establishment, ethnic/cultural background, familiarity, treatment of sub-clinical or otherwise untreated illness",
        "answer": "trust of the medical establishment",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are typical supplement users",
		"choices": "female, more educated, recently hospitalized, former smokers, all of the above, none of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "In order to know if dietary supplements are effective you need to know your e____, encourage r____ expectations, keep the patient as a w____ in mind",
        "answer": "evidence, realistic, whole",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some examples of evidence: l____/e____/g____ resource",
        "answer": "literature, electronic, government",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not an electronic literature source",
		"choices": "Natural Medicines Database, Facts and Comparisons, Wikipedia, Micromedex, Cochrane reviews",
        "answer": "Wikipedia",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dietary supplements are regulated by the FDA under the provisions of ____",
        "answer": "DSHEA",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "A dietary supplement label may not claim that the supplement can d____, p____, m____, t____, or c____a specific disease",
        "answer": "diagnose, prevent, mitigate, treat, cure",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Exceptions are made for which specific health claims which need to meet Federal guidelines",
		"choices": "approved health claims, qualified health claims, nutrient claims, well-being claims, none of the above, all of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dietary supplements can be labeled in regard to prevention of d____ disease, s____ or f____, or in regard to w____-b____",
        "answer": "deficiency, structure, function, well-being",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government resources include",
		"choices": "Both FDA and NIH, National Institutes of Health, Office of Dietary Supplements: Fact Sheets, Medline Plus, all of the above, none of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "An appropiate response to is dietary supplements safe is",
		"choices": "be aware of risks, keep relative risks in perspective, minimize risk, keep lines of communication open, report risks, all of the above, none of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "For interactions, you must pay attention to the same e____, same s____ e____, same m____",
        "answer": "effect, side effect, metabolism",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Factual content of advertising is monitored by the ____ and ____",
        "answer": "FDA, FTC",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the best response for dietary substances regulated by the FDA",
		"choices": "be aware of variateions in manufacturer standards, be aware of standardization, help patients find quality products, be aware of likely areas of contamination, all of the above, none of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    }
]